# EMAIL: <u>MMSOUZA114@GMAIL.COM</u> PERSONAL WEBSITE: <u>MONIQUESOUZA.COM</u>

# MONIQUE M. SOUZA

## **OBJECTIVE**

My objective is to be employed within a company which will allow me to utilize my experience and skills in providing effective and comprehensive support.

### SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Extensive experience in Microsoft Word, Excel, Power Point, Outlook, Desk.com, Adobe Acrobat, POS, Cyber Source Verification Software, Web link Sales Software, Numeric and Alpha Data Entry. Type 50+ wpm. Strong communication, organizational and interpersonal skills. Entry level knowledge of programming languages of Swift, Java and Python, knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript and some jQuery and Bootstrap. Knowledgeable of Linux and bash scripting and GitHub. Some Salesforce knowledge.

#### TECHNICAL EXPERIENCE

- Currently Front-end lead to small group of software engineers to create and deploy small inhouse e-commerce infrastructure. Completion date December 2019.
- Small personal projects in web development on my own to learn front-end languages that can be found on my GitHub account: <a href="https://github.com/Momomartinez">https://github.com/Momomartinez</a>
- Mobile app in Swift programming language along with XCode experience spring 2019.
- Small programming assignments with Java and C++ from semesters 2016 to 2017 also found on GitHub account.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

■ August 2016 – Present Residential Coordinator

Life Moves

San Mateo, Ca

I assist at a homeless shelter for families. Providing a welcoming and safe environment for the families coming in and out. As well as working with case managers and assisting them with their casework.

Bay Alarm Co.

Glendale, CA

Service/Field Coordinator

Schedule and Coordinate installations with customers, installers, and sales representatives. Maintain and distribute schedule for installers. Assist the Service Dept. and the Install Dept. Review and process completed work orders to cooperate for billing and other miscellaneous paperwork. Maintain work-in-progress and billing and billing records daily.

■ May 2009 – June 2011

Menchies

Sherman Oaks, CA

Store Manager

Managed a small staff and ensured productivity. Counted cash boxes and made drops, opened and closed shop.

#### **EDUCATION**

2015 - Present

San Francisco State University

Bachelor's Degree in Philosophy emphasis in law and minor in Computer Science in progress

(Expected graduation 2019)

San Francisco City, CA

2010 - 2012

Los Angeles Valley College

Associates Degree

Van Nuys, CA

2004 - 2008

Valley Alternative Magnet

High School Diploma

Van Nuys, CA

#### LANGUAGES

English and some Spanish

#### VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Valley Presbyterian Hospital Volunteer, Santa Rosa Youth Lector, and Feed LA.

#### REFERENCES

Provided upon request